// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which of the following food types would most likely give a negative result upon addition of iodine solution?",
    answer: "Butter",
    options: [
      "Bread",
      "Butter",
      "Biscuit",
      "Potato"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which process produces mRNA during protein synthesis?",
    answer:  "Transcription",
    options: [
      " Translation",
      " Replication",
      "Mutation",
      "Transcription"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the molecule in plant cells that first captures the radiant energy from sunlight?",
    answer:  " Chlorophyll",
    options: [
      "ATP",
      " DNA",
      " Chlorophyll",
      "Carbon dioxide"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which of the following laboratory glassware is used for culturing bacteria?",
    answer: "Petri dish",
    options: [
      "Petri dish",
      "Test tube",
      "Filter paper",
      " Measuring cylinder"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct sequence of the steps in scientific research?",
    answer: "Question -> hypothesis formulation -> experiment -> conclusion",
    options: [
      "Hypothesis formulation -> conclusion -> experiment -> question",
      "Question -> hypothesis formulation -> experiment -> conclusion",
      "Hypothesis formulation -> question -> experiment -> conclusion",
      "Question -> hypothesis formulation -> conclusion -> experiment"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In cell division, what is the phase that comes following the metaphase called? ",
    answer:"Anaphase",
    options: [
      "Extraphase",
      "Prophase",
      "Anaphase",
      "Telophase"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which of the following is made of globular proteins?",
    answer: "Enzyme",
    options: [
      "Enzyme",
      "Keratin",
      "Collagen",
      "Glycogen"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " In the carbon cycle, which of the following processes removes carbon dioxide from the atmosphere? ",
    answer: "Photosynthesis",
    options: [
      "Respiration",
      "Decomposition",
      "Combustion",
      "Photosynthesis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following processes releases CO2 into the atmosphere? ",
    answer:"Respiration",
    options: [
      "Respiration",
      "Assimilation",
      "Feeding",
      "Photosynthesis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one of the following functions best at higher optimum pH than all the rest? ",
    answer: "Enzymes in stomach",
    options: [
      " Pepsin",
      "Salivary amylase",
      "Trypsin",
      "Enzymes in stomach"
    ]
  },






];